KELVIN MARCUS MICKENS TECHNICAL ANALYST

904-323-8684 MICKENSKM@GMAIL.COM

WORK PROFILE

Navy Veteran Executive Administrative Manager, served as the point of contact for all employees, providing administrative support, and managing their queries. Expert organizational skills include managing office, preparing reports, and organizing company records. Hardworking, knowledgeable, and dedicated employee. Fit for any work environment and welcomes all challenges.

KEY EXPERTISE

- Network Systems
- Computer Hardware
- Indoctrination Coordinator
- Policies & Regulatory Compliance
- Expert Knowledge of MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, & SharePoint
- Recreations Management
- Defense Travel System Expert
- · Personnel Readiness Coordinator
- Staff Supervision & Counseling
- MS Outlook Support
- · Payroll Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bank of America Technical Support October 2020-Current

KEY ROLES

- -Servicing Customer's VPN/Access Issues
- -Troubleshooting issues with Customer Accounts (WebEx, SharePoint, Internet, Shared Drive)
- -Remote connection/Remote Desktop restoration (VMware/Citrix)
- -Corp Phone and Token Administration
- -Providing over the phone support and walk-thru problem resolution with customers
- -Technical support for customers over the phone
- -Draft, submitting, and working troubleshooting tickets
- -Chat tech support specialist

Citibank Call Center Representative/Sales From October 2018-April 2020

United States Navy (Active Duty)
Administrative Manager
From December 2008 To February 2018

SKILLS

A. Technical Support

- Experienced and knowledgeable information technology professional with 3+ years' experience.
- Perform diagnostics and troubleshooting of multiple issues, document help desk tickets/resolutions, and maintain equipment inventory lists.

B. Customer Service

- As call center rep, serviced over 600 calls a month
- 95-110% Ticket to Call, 98% First Call Resolution
- Provided immediate support and troubleshooting assistance across various platforms.

C. Training Coordinator

- As Training Coordinator, facilitated the training for over 200 personnel to ensure all annual training was completed with 100% completion.
- Managed the completion of training to include: scheduling, venue, facilitators, attendance, and electronic tracking of all training required.

D. Budget Analyst, Travel Coordinator

- Maintained annual budgets of \$5 Million in allocated funds for over 200 Training Exercise, Conferences, and Deployments.
- Expert level of knowledge of the Defense Travel System planned, established, and executed travel arrangements and allocated, budgeted, and liquidated fiscal year funds.
- As Citi Bank Manager, maintained the accounts for over 600 personnel with zero deficiencies and 100% accountability of all fiscal year budgets.

E. HR Management

- Served as the Indoctrination Coordinator, monitored the "Welcome Aboard" onboarding program for over 600 personnel coming in and out, ensuring personnel were properly trained prior to starting jobs and administrative paper work was completed.
- As HR Manager, ensured all hires had the skills required to perform assigned jobs and were in the appropriate billet. Managed the payroll for over 600 personnel.

F. Logistic Manager

- Operated Forklift to complete stocking and monitored all department supplies. As the Logistic Manager, maintained an accurate account of all items required for the company. Maintained 100% accountability of the supplies and logged all transactions.
- As Mail Manager, originated, processed, and maintained records of all items shipped and received. Handled of 2 million pounds of mail and ensured distribution.

CERTIFICATIONS & MILITARY QUALIFICATIONS

- ITIL 4
- Customer Service (US Navy)
- Travel Clerk (US Navy)
- Security Manager (US Navy)
- Legal Secretary (2200 HR Certification)
- Computer Operations (2000 HR Certification)
- Special Security Specialist
- Correspondence (US Navy)
- Legal Clerk (US Navy)
- Administrative Manager (US Navy)
- Officer/Administrative Manager (4000 HR Certification)
- Pay and Personnel Administrator

EDUCATION

- WGU (2023)
 - Bachelors in Computer Science

AWARDS

- 4 Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medals
- 5 Navy Sailor of the Ouarter Awards
- 5 Flag Letters of Commendation
- 5 Employee's of the month Bank of America